Finding aid for the The Ohio State University Health Sciences Library Records
Medical Heritage Center
- Series II: Collections (6 boxes) consists of files and newsletters that relate to the books and information available through the Health Sciences Library. This is mostly found through a large amount of administrative statistics that reference aspects such as circulation, digital databases and even
  - Annual Report: Collection Development, 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report: Serials, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Appraisals, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Area Health Education Center, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Area Health Education Center, 1983-1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ariel, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Ariel, No Date (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - ARL, 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - ARL (File 1 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - ARL (File 2 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - ARL, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - ARL (File 1 of 2), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - ARL (File 2 of 2), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - ARL, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Artifact Collection, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Circuit Librarian, 2001-2006 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Circuit Librarian Reports, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Circulation General Information, 1991-2002 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Circulation Statistics, 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Cleveland Clinic Affiliation, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Cleveland Clinic Affiliation, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Cleveland Clinic Document Delivery, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Closed Reserve, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - COHLC, 1988-1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - COHSLA Business Meeting, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Columbus Hospital Consortium, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - COMIN, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Community Education/Corporate Wellness, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Complaints, 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Computers in Research Committee, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Confidentiality Patron Records Policy, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Copy Center, 1989-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Copy Machines, 1998-2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Core Functions, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Courtesy Cards, 1978-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Database Usage and Services, 1987-1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Disability Services, 1985-1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - DocMD Project, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Document Delivery Move, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Evidence Based Medicine (File 1 of 2), 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Evidence Based Medicine (File 2 of 2), 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Exhibit Planning, 1963-1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - File Cataloging, 1993-1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Goodale Storage Facility, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Gopher, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Harding Hospital, 1994-2001 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - History Center Proposals, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - History of Medicine, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - History Room, 1981-1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Independent Study Programs, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Independent Study Programs, Library Space, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Indirect Cost Study, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Information Center Proposal, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Interlibrary Loan, 1977-1992 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Interlibrary Loan (File 1 of 2), 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Interlibrary Loan (File 2 of 2), 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - JCAHO Accreditation Manual for Hospitals, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Journal Cancellations, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Journal Subscription, 1986-2003 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Lab Books, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - LCS: Manual, No Date (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - LCS: Renewal and Save Instructions, No Date (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - LEXIS/NEXIS, 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Library Health Information, 1994-2006 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Library Support for MedFlight, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - LibQual+ Project, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - LibQual+ Project, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - LibQual+ Summary Report The Ohio State University Libraries, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - LibQual+ Survey Results AAHSL, Spring 2002 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - LibQual+ Survey Results AAHSL, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - LibQual+ Survey Results Aggregate, Spring 2002 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - LibQual+ Survey Results ARL, Spring 2002 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - LibQual+ Survey Results Ohio State University Health Sciences Library, Spring 2002 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - LibQual+ Survey Results Ohio State University Health Sciences Library, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - MedCentral Health System, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Medical Books Approval Plan, 1985-2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - MEDLARS, 1964-1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - MEDLARS: Budget and Training, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Mid-Ohio Health Sciences Librarians, 1990-1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Mutilated Books, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - OCLC, No Date (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - OhioLINK Agreement for an Automated Library System, June 4, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - OhioLINK Policy Handbook, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - OPHILTP, 1985-2005 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - OSU: Faculty and Staff Awards, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Patron Head Count, 1982-1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Personnel Requests and Projections, 1959-1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Power Pages, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Primary Clientele, 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Program of Requirements: Health Sciences Library Rehabilitation, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Reference, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - References, 1987-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - RIST Future of Reference, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - RIST Information, 1998-2002 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - RIST Minutes, 1998-2004 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - RIST Webpages, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship and Learning in Transition: A Self-Study of the Moritz, Prior, and University Libraries, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 22.1)
  - Statistics, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Statistics, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Statistics, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Statistics: AAHSL, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Statistics: AAHSL, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Statistics: ARL (File 1 of 2), 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Statistics: ARL (File 2 of 2), 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Statistics: ARL, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Statistics: Booleans, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Statistics: Circulation, 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Statistics: Circulation, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Statistics: Circulation, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Statistics: Copy Center, 1985-1993 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Statistics: Document Delivery, 1995-2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Statistics: HEA, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Statistics: Info Desk, 1988-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Statistics: IPEDS, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Statistics: Medical Library Statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Statistics: Medical Library Statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1995-1996 (Box 9.1, Folder 1)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1996-1997 (Box 9.1, Folder 2)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1997-1998 (Box 9.1, Folder 3)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1998-1999 (Box 9.1, Folder 4)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 1999-2000 (Box 9.1, Folder 5)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2000-2001 (Box 9.1, Folder 6)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2001-2002 (Box 9.1, Folder 7)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2002-2003 (Box 9.1, Folder 8)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2003-2004 (Box 9.1, Folder 9)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2005-2006 (Box 9.1, Folder 10)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2006-2007 (Box 9.1, Folder 11)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2007-2008 (Box 9.1, Folder 12)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2008-2009 (Box 9.1, Folder 13)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2009-2010 (Box 9.1, Folder 14)
  - Statistics: Medical School Libraries in the United States and Canada, 2010-2011 (Box 9.1, Folder 15)
  - Statistics: MEDLARS (File 1 of 2), 1967-1972 (Box 9.1, Folder 16)
  - Statistics: MEDLARS (File 2 of 2), 1967-1972 (Box 9.1, Folder 17)
  - Statistics: Preservation, 1988 (Box 9.1, Folder 18)
  - Statistics: Serials, 1989-1990 (Box 9.1, Folder 19)
  - Statistics: Subject Evaluation, 1990-1994 (Box 9.1, Folder 20)
  - Surveys, 1978-2006 (Box 9.1, Folder 21)
  - Topaz Closing, 1986-1988 (Box 9.1, Folder 22)
  - Topaz Gift Journals, 1989 (Box 9.1, Folder 23)
  - University Insurance Policy, 1994 (Box 9.1, Folder 24)
  - University Library System Academic Support Unit Program Review, Internal Unit Review Panel Final Report, 2006 (Box 9.1, Folder 25)
- Series III: Construction (7 boxes) holds a wide variety of documents pertaining to the original construction of the Health Sciences Library as well as the renovations that followed. However, the majority of the collection is in relation to the renovations rather than the original construction project from 1969. The three most abundant themes in this series are broken down into: Relocation, Correspondence and Furniture, and once again these are mostly referencing the renovation projects. Most of the remaining documents are related to administrative decisions or files containing reports, budgets or correspondence with specific contractors. This series is arranged alphabetically., 1967-2008
  - Acock Associates Architects Proposals + Interview, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Acock: Design Development Submittal, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Acock: Kick-Off Meeting Minutes, February 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Acock: Phase 1-Relocation, Meeting Notes, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Acock: Project Manual, Vol. 1 of 2, August 2008 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Acock: Specifications (File 1 of 2), March 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Acock: Specifications (File 2 of 2), March 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Acock: Specifications; Pre-Bid, No Date (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Acock: Specifications, Vol. 1 of 2 (File 1 of 2), May 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Acock: Specifications, Vol. 1 of 2 (File 2 of 2), May 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Acock: Specifications, Vol. 2 of 2, May 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Acock: Warranty Complaints, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Addenda to Plans and Specifications, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Application for Construction Grant (File 1 of 2), December 1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Application for Construction Grant (File 2 of 2), December 1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Art, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - ASI Sign Systems, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Ask Desk, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Audio-Visual Renovation, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Basement Access, April 1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Board of Regents, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Building Audit Report, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Building Directory Design, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 23.1)
  - Building Renovation Committee: Public Lockers, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Building Renovation Input, No Date (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Building Request: Taylor Renee, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Building Schematics, No Date (Box 10, Folder 26.1)
  - Building Statistics, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Building Statistics, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Building Story, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Building Working File, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Building Working File, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Campus Building Tours, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Campus Cards, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Collection Management Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Computer Lab Renovation, 1994-2004 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Conduit Systems Specs, No Date (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Confidential Consulting Report: IDS, No Date (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Construction Blog for the Prior Renovation Project, 2010-2012 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Construction Cost Estimate, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Construction Document Review, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Construction Plans for Health Science Library, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Design Development, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Electrical Operation and Maintenance Reference Manual: Book 1, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Electrical Operation and Maintenance Reference Manual: Book 2, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Electrical Operation and Maintenance Reference Manual: Book 3, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Electrical Operation and Maintenance Reference Manual: Book 4, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Electrical Operation and Maintenance Reference Manual: Book 5 (File 1 of 2), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Electrical Operation and Maintenance Reference Manual: Book 5 (File 2 of 2), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Electrical Operation and Maintenance Reference Manual: Book 6, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Estimated Project Timeline, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - External Review Committee: Report, October 1989 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Facility Audit Report, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Federal Standards, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Final Details, 1990-1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Floor Plans, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Focus Group, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Furniture: Aaron Cohen Associates, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Furniture: Acock Associates, Inc., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Furniture: Acquisitions, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Furniture: Acquisitions, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Furniture: Bretford Product Guide, No Date (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Furniture: Columbus Show Case Company, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Furniture: Gressco Product Catalog, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Furniture: Inventory, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Furniture: Legacy Library Systems, No Date (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Furniture: Library Design Associates, No Date (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Furniture: Office, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Furniture: Planning, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Furniture: Planning, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Furniture: Richard Trott and Partners, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Furniture: Samples, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Furniture: Scania Contract Library Furniture, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Furniture: Shelving, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Furniture: Steelcase, No Date (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Furniture: Thomas W. Ruff & Co., No Date (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Furniture: Thos. Moser Cabinetmakers, No Date (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Furniture: Wandel & Schnell, Architects, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - HSL Construction and Move from Hamilton Hall, 1968-1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Improvements (File 1 of 2), 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Improvements (File 2 of 2), 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Knowledge Building Committee Report, December 1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Library Task Force, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3.1)
  - Lighting, 1990-1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Lobby Projects, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Management Studies Report, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - MD Consult Pilot Test, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes (File 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes (File 2 of 2), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Memorandum of Understanding, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Microcomputer Laboratory, 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Move Committees, No Date (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Move Consultation and Planning, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mural, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - National Library Relocations, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - New Journal Area, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Articles About Library Renovations, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Non-Access Services in Temporary Location, No Date (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - OCLC Telecommunications Planning, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - OSU Communications Wiring Standard, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - OSU Modifications and Schematics: Column Cabinets (File 1 of 3), No Date (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - OSU Modifications and Schematics: Column Cabinets (File 2 of 3), No Date (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - OSU Modifications and Schematics: Column Cabinets (File 3 of 3), No Date (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - OSU Modifications and Schematics: Console Cabinets (File 1 of 2), No Date (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - OSU Modifications and Schematics: Console Cabinets (File 2 of 2), No Date (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - “OSU on the Move”, University Budget and Space Planning, December 1994 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - OSU Purchasing Department: Hallett Movers, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - OTIS Owner’s Manual, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Planning and Evaluation Guidelines for Academic Health Sciences Libraries, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Plans for Artwork in HSL, 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Plans for Computer Lab, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Plans for Reference Services, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Presentations and Reports: Library Design and Planning, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Program of Requirements, March 1984-January 1993 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Program of Requirements (File 1 of 2), March-July 1993 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Program of Requirements (File 2 of 2), March-July 1993 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Program of Requirements, August-November 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Program of Requirements, January 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Program of Requirements, February 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Program of Requirements, April 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Program of Requirements: Guidelines, July 1984-October 1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Program of Requirements: Revisions, No Date (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Proposal for Self inform Directory, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Publicity of Library to JORCS, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Readings: Library Design and Planning, 1983-1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Readings: Library Design and Planning, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Readings: University of Arizona Health Sciences Library, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Readings: University of California, Irvine Science Library, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Readings: Vanderbilt University Biomedical Library, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Readings: Washington University Health Science Library, 1986-1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Readings: Yale University Medical Library, 1985-1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Rededication, April 1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Rededication Symposium, April 25, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Relocation: Debrief after Move to JORCS, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Relocation: Goodale Storage Facility, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Relocation: JORCS Improvements, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Relocation: Map, No Date (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Relocation: Move Survey, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Relocation: Move to JORCS (File 1 of 3), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Relocation: Move to JORCS (File 2 of 3), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Relocation: Move to JORCS (File 3 of 3), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Relocation: Move to JORCS Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Relocation: Planning, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Relocation: Returning to the HSL from JORCS (File 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Relocation: Returning to the HSL from JORCS (File 2 of 2), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Relocation: William B. Meyer, Inc., Library Moving Division; Bid, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Renovation Notes, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Renovation Suggestions, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Renovations, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Requisition, No Date (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Requisition, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Roof, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 10.1)
  - Schedule of Spaces, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Shelving Equipment, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Space Planning, 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Staff Edits, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Staff Edits, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Staff Involved in Planning the Move, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Staff Schematic Comments, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Staff Support Committee Temporary Relocation Team, December 1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Self Study Committee: Plan of Action, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Self Study Committee: Report, January 1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Self Study Committee: Suggested Style Guide, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Study Carrel Report, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 21.1)
  - Technology, 1991-1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Technology Committee Meetings, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - TRT: Access to Materials, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - TRT: Executive Report, No Date (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - TRT: Move Committee (File 1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - TRT: Move Committee (File 2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - TTSS Electronic Directories, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Type of Space, No Date (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Type of Space: Draft, No Date (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Type of Space: Outline, No Date (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Wiring Diagrams, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Working Information, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - C. Curtiss Inscho: Specifications, Legal Sized, November 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)